orderstore.in 2016-03-15

# Privacy Policy

**Information**  
We collect all the information submitted by the customers to serve them better. We guarantee that your personal information is not shared with any third party for commercial use.Our aim is only to collect such information which reflects our customers behaviors and patterns which we would utilize to improve our services for them.  
Source of Our Information  
The details shared by you at the time of registration, feedback provided by you on our services, and the transactions made along the payment card details are our information sources. We also collect the information through the competitions, promotions, and the traffic that our site generates. This approach helps us to provide better products and services to our customers.  
 **Information Use**  
The information would be used for helping us in customizing and personalizing the services for our customers.The information can also be used to communicate the customers the latest offers and schemes, news and events, products and services updates. Personal information is shared for our online payment gateway providers, as they would require for risk monitoring purposes. Sometimes it will get necessary to communicate to our customers, to inform them about any important changes in the products and services. We may also require feedback and suggestions from you. Hence, we can communicate to you by post, e-mail, phone, etc.  
 **Cookies:**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  
 **Security:**  
Your credit card information is processed over secure gateways. We have been very particular in choosing the gateway, as this is one of the most important things. Your credit card information is not stored in our servers.We only store the payment id.  
 **Other web sites and links:**  
There may be links present in our website, which does not fall under our arena of control and privacy policy. Clicking on such links would lead and bind you to follow the privacy policy of their website; we would not be responsible for any misuse of the information collected by them about you.

  Loading...
